Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Financial records, 1985 - 1992; F-225-5; 7 cm of textual records
  - Budget, 1989 - 1990; F-225-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
  - Budget, 1990 - 1991; F-225-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
  - Budget, 1991 - 1992; F-225-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
- Scholarships, awards and bursaries, 1966 - 1988; F-225-6; 68 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the administration of graduate scholarships, awards and bursaries offered by SFU, private citizens and companies, and national granting agencies such as the Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council (SSHRC) and the National Science and Engineering Research Council (NSERC). Records include terms of reference, adjudication guidelines, correspondence, working papers, reports, and financial statements.
  Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council; Natural Science and Engineering Research Council
  - General student scholarships, awards and bursaries, 1966 - 1988; F-225-6-1; 28 cm of textual records
    - Leon J. Ladner Graduate Scholarship in History, 1966 - 1984; F-225-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-42.
    - Sidney Hogg Memorial Scholarship, 1967 - 1971; F-225-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-47.
    - Canron Limited - Sidney Hogg Memorial Scholarship, 1967 - 1971; F-225-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-11.
    - Canada Council Doctoral Fellowship Awards, vol. 1, 1970 - 1978; F-225-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-2.
    - Canada Council Doctoral Fellowship Awards, vol. 2, 1970 - 1978; F-225-6-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-1.
    - Xerox of Canada Graduate Scholarship, 1971 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-62.
    - B.C. Council of Garden Clubs, 1976 - 1983; F-225-6-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-3.
    - Vancouver Horticultural Society Bursary, 1977 - 1979; F-225-6-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-60.
    - Weldwood of Canada Graduate Scholarship, 1978 - 1979; F-225-6-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-19.
    - Graduate Research, Engineering and Technology Awards, vol. 1, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-11.
    - Graduate Research, Engineering and Technology Awards, vol. 2, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-12.
    - Graduate Research, Engineering and Technology Awards, vol. 3, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-15.
    - C.D. Nelson Memorial Scholarship, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-6.
    - H.R. MacMillan Family Fund Scholarship, vol. 1, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-26.
    - H.R. MacMillan Family Fund Scholarship, vol. 2, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-27.
    - H.R. MacMillan Family Fund Scholarship, vol. 3, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-28.
    - H.R. MacMillan Family Fund Scholarship, vol. 4, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-29.
    - Cook Conference Scholarship, 1979 - 1982; F-225-6-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-18.
    - B.C. Packers Limited Scholarship, 1979 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-5.
    - CN - Terry Fox Research Fellowship, 1980 - 1984; F-225-6-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-7.
    - International Development Research Centre, 1980 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-18.
    - Bert Henry Memorial Graduate Scholarship, 1980 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-1.
    - Walter E. Heller Financial Corporation Scholarship, 1981 - 1982; F-225-6-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-61.
    - Gordon Diewert Graduate Scholarship in Kinesiology, 1981 - 1984; F-225-6-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-24.
    - Northern Scientific Training Program Grant, vol. 1, 1981 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-27.
    - Northern Scientific Training Program Grant, vol. 2, 1981 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-28.
    - Northern Scientific Training Program Grant, vol. 3, 1981 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-29.
    - Northern Scientific Training Program Grant, vol. 4, 1981 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-30.
    - Graduate Research Fellowships, 1983 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-33.
    - I.O.D.E. Seaman Morley Scott Graduate Scholarship, 1983 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 225-31)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-40.
    - NATO Postgraduate Fellowship, 1984; F-225-6-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-17.
    - SFU Disabled Graduate Student Award, 1984 - 1985; F-225-6-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-2-0-56.
    - Canadian Environmental Assessment Research Council Graduate Research Contract, vol. 1, 1984 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-8.
    - Canadian Environmental Assessment Research Council Graduate Research Contract, vol. 2, 1984 - 1986; F-225-6-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-4-0-9.
    - R.H. Wright Award in Olfactory Research, vol. 1, 1984 - 1988; F-225-6-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
    - R.H. Wright Award in Olfactory Research, vol. 2, 1984 - 1988; F-225-6-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
    - R.H. Wright Award in Olfactory Research, vol. 3, 1984 - 1988; F-225-6-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
    - R.H. Wright Award in Olfactory Research, vol. 4, 1984 - 1988; F-225-6-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
  - Graduate student stipends, 1971 - 1985; F-225-6-2; 8 cm of textual records
    - Graduate student budget, 1971 - 1975; F-225-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-52.
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1974 - 1985; F-225-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-46.
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1974 - 1985; F-225-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-47.
    - Terms of reference, 1976 - 1985; F-225-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-44.
    - Statistics, 1977 - 1982; F-225-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-54.
    - Policies, 1978 - 1982; F-225-6-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-45.
    - Projections, 1981 - 1982; F-225-6-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-65.
    - Correspondence with Senate committees, vol. 1, 1981 - 1982; F-225-6-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-50.
    - Correspondence with Senate committees, vol. 2, 1981 - 1982; F-225-6-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-51.
  - Open graduate scholarships, 1975 - 1985; F-225-6-3; 3 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1975 - 1981; F-225-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-85.
    - Recipients master list, 1979 - 1985; F-225-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-89.
    - Budget, 1980 - 1985; F-225-6-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-87.
    - Correspondence, 1982 - 1985; F-225-6-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-1-0-86.
  - SSHRC scholarships, 1978 - 1986; F-225-6-4; 3 cm of textual records
    - Doctoral fellowships recipients' lists, 1978 - 1984; F-225-6-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-31.
    - Special M.A. scholarship, 1978 - 1985; F-225-6-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-32.
    - Doctoral fellowship correspondence, 1979 - 1983; F-225-6-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
    - Award holders, 1984 - 1986; F-225-6-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-34.
  - NSERC scholarships, 1978 - 1987; F-225-6-5; 25 cm of textual records
    - University Selection Committee, 1978; F-225-6-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-3.
    - External correspondence, 1979; F-225-6-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-5.
    - Internal correspondence, 1979 - 1980; F-225-6-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-4.
    - External correspondence, 1980 - 1982; F-225-6-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-33)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-6.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, vol. 1, 1980 - 1982; F-225-6-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-18.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, vol. 2, 1980 - 1982; F-225-6-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-19.
    - Postgraduate scholarships, vol. 1, 1980 - 1986; F-225-6-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-10.
    - Postgraduate scholarships, vol. 2, 1980 - 1986; F-225-6-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-11.
    - Postgraduate scholarships recipient lists, 1980 - 1986; F-225-6-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-9.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, 1981 - 1982; F-225-6-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-20.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, 1982 - 1983; F-225-6-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-21.
    - Postgraduate scholarships and postdoctoral fellowships - misc, 1982 - 1983; F-225-6-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-16.
    - Postgraduate scholarships, 1982 - 1984; F-225-6-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-34)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-12.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, 1983 - 1984; F-225-6-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-22.
    - Postgraduate scholarships, 1983 - 1984; F-225-6-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-13.
    - Postgraduate scholarships, 1984 - 1985; F-225-6-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-14.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, vol. 1, 1984 - 1986; F-225-6-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-24.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, vol. 2, 1984 - 1986; F-225-6-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-23.
    - Undergraduate summer research awards, vol. 3, 1984 - 1986; F-225-6-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-25.
    - Postgraduate scholarships, 1985 - 1987; F-225-6-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-11-3-0-15.
- Publications, 1970 - 2000; F-225-7; 16 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies. Records include annual graduate studies fact books and graduate student handbooks, graduate program brochures, a guide to graduate awards, graduate studies regulation handbooks, and reports on the citizenship of graduate students, survey of graduate studies at SFU, and guidelines on the preparation of theses, essays and projects.
  The publications found in this series were acquired by the Archives from a variety of sources. Although the accessions from the Dean of Graduate Studies contained a number of departmental publications, most of the publications were collected by Archives staff as part of an artificial university-wide periodicals collection and then processed as part of the fonds.
  - Graduate Studies General Regulations Handbook, 1970 - 1978; F-225-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
  - Forestry Related Activities at SFU, 1980 - 1983; F-225-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
  - Communication and Communications Technology Research at SFU, 1981 - 1983; F-225-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-35)
  - Preparation of Theses, Extended Essays and Projects, Regulations and Guidelines, 1988; F-225-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Report on the Citizenship of Current SFU Graduate Students, 1990; F-225-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Fact Book, 1991; F-225-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Handbook, 1991 - 1992; F-225-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Fact Book, 1992; F-225-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Fact Book, 1993; F-225-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Handbook, 1993 - 1994; F-225-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - SFU Graduate Program brochures, [199-?] - [200-?]; F-225-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Fact Book, 1994; F-225-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Handbook, 1994 - 1995; F-225-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Fact Book, 1995; F-225-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Handbook, 1995 - 1996; F-225-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Handbook, 1996 - 1997; F-225-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Studies Handbook, 1997 - 1998; F-225-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Award Guide, 1997 - 1998; F-225-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-36)
  - Graduate Students at SFU - Report of the Graduate Survey Committee, 1998; F-225-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-36)